[{"answer": "I did.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "And be honest, when you knew you'd won the bid and you saw the Beijing Olympics' opening ceremony, did you think, what the hell are we going to do to beat that?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well, it's a very good question and a very difficult one to answer.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "But also just generally in that region?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Well, I think, first of all, we have to understand what's going on in the region.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "How concerned should people be about the spread of the influence of the Muslim Brotherhood?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Essentially, I mean, I agree that a nuclear armed Iran is a devastating thing for the region.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "How much do you agree with Israel's fear and concern about the nature of Iran's threat?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Well, the first thing to understand is Israel will protect its own interest.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "And if Israel decides to act unilaterally, which they have threatened to do, where would that leave everybody in the Middle East?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "It's -- it's very, very difficult.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Because there's a general acceptance that Assad must go, but how is he going to go?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "I think it's still strong.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "How is the special relationship in reality do you think between America and Britain these days?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "Look, if the American elections for you guys is not for us guys.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "How are you reading the political ruins at the moment in Washington?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Deeply perilous.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "How perilous is the situation when you look at Europe in totality?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "And should it be saved?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "I think it does rest on what Germany does, yes.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "But is it an exaggeration to say that in her hands, the future, certainly in the short term and middle term of the whole European economy could rest on what Germany does?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "Well, I don't -- you know -- look, I don't want to enter into a controversy that must be difficult for people in America right now.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "I think the Americans have got to decide this.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "But do you think, though, that high-powered assault weapons and magazine drums capable of unloading a hundred bullets a minute, is it right that they should still be legally accessible?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "I work out a lot.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "How do you do it?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Not every day.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Every day, is it?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Let's wait and see if it does.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "But what it comes your way again?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Well, you rarely get moments of success.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "When you look back over your whole career, if I could let you relive one moment of success again, what one moment would you choose?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's got a huge challenge for itself and for the world.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "What would be the things you'd like to talk to him about?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "For the sake of Pakistan.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Why would you do that?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "It was.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Well, I think it has made Pakistan more dangerous now.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Has the Afghanistan war been successful or has it, arguably, made Pakistan even more understandable and even more dangerous?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "Yes, that -- I totally agree with you, that it is not believable.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "What does Pakistan do about that, to try and rebuild that trust?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "No, I don't think so.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Is that -- is that likely?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "-- that he might be?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't call it the most dangerous place in the world.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "When you hear Mitt Romney, who may well be president come November, talking of Iran being the most dangerous place on Earth now and the prospect of them getting nuclear weapons making it even more dangerous, what is your reaction?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Well, Iran would argue they do have threats.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "So why go nuclear?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Well -- well, first of all, Israel doesn't have a border with Iran.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "I mean if Israel is allowed nuclear weapons, if Pakistan are, if you're in Iran, Ahmadinejad, he would argue -- I've heard him say this -- if these other countries are allowed to have nuclear weapons, why can't I?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Well, I think so much has happened in -- in interfering in various countries of the Muslim world, I would say, that I think that external interference has never produced good results.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Isn't there a -- a moral compulsion now to get in there?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Well, I would like to -- generally in Pakistan, people believe that Republicans have always been favorably disposed toward Pakistan, more than the Democrats.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Who would you prefer to win?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "Well, no, not really.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "So you're a -- you're a Romney man?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Difficult question to answer.", "docId": "120725pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "But from all you've seen and heard of President Obama and Mitt Romney, which one do you think would best suit the interests of Pakistan over the next four years?", "qSentId": 486}]